sharegyan.com 2008-06-30

# Privacy Policy - ShareGyan.com

**Highlights:** 1\. Do intraday trading only for few days.   2 **.** Try to book profit at regular intervals only. 

**Yahoo! ID - sharegyan**  
(Add Now)

## Guests

We do not collect any personal information on this website. However, our web server logs all visitor information and we use this for statistical purposes.

## Members/Subscribers

We collect your personal data such as Name, email, phone number etc. for contacting you. We will not share your e-mail address with anyone. It will only be used to send you stock market tips and newsletters. You may opt-out of these at any time by unsubscribing to our services.

## INTRODUCTION

We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

We respect each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website. For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

Registration is not required to enter our site. However, subscription to certain services may require a user to complete a registration form. During registration a user must give certain contact information, but we never sell or give away this information. It is only gathered to contact the users about services on our site for which s/he has expressed interest.

We do show advertisement to our users, which are handled by third party providers. The contents on the advertised links are beyond our control and we are not responsible for it in any form.

So any such concerns with our advertising should be directed towards them respectfully. 

## NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. 

## CONFLICT RESOLUTION

We are committed to resolving disputes within 48-72 hours. If problems arise, users may contact via our contact form. 

## Contact Us

Name (Required)  
  
Email (Required)  
  
Mobile Number (Required)

Attention (Choose the right department)  

Mail Message  

Please note that all fields marked as _Required_ must be filled.  
Also this form is not for trial requests visit trial request page if you want to [register for free trial](http://www.sharegyan.com/indian-stock-market/free-trial/).   
---
